Contact

+91 750 700 0107 (Mobile) kunalvani172000@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/kunal-wani-0107 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Growth Marketing Build Website Blogger

Certifications

Digital and Growth Marketing Workshop

Scientific Computing with Python Use Canva to Create Desktop and Mobile-friendly Web Pages.

Kunal Wani

Digital Marketing Strategist | Trainer | Agency Owner at Gyani Master Digital Technologies | SEO Expert | Google Ads and Facebook Ads Expert | Web Developer | Content Writer | Nashik, Maharashtra, India

Summary

I'm Kunal Wani, a passionate digital marketer with experience in crafting successful online strategies for businesses. I wear multiple hats - I run Gyani Master Digital Technologies, a digital marketing agency that helps businesses thrive online through SEO, Facebook Ads, Google Ads, Website Design & Development, and Social Media Management. I also actively share my knowledge as a digital marketing trainer.

- What I Do:
- Grow Brands & Businesses Online
- Develop & Implement Strategic Digital Marketing Plans
- Drive Traffic & Conversions through SEO, Paid Ads & Social Media
- Design & Develop User-Friendly Websites
- Manage & Optimize Social Media Presence
- Connect with me if you're looking to:
- Increase brand awareness and website traffic
- Generate leads and sales through digital channels
- Improve your website's ranking and user experience
- Build a strong social media presence

I'm always happy to chat about digital marketing and explore how I can help your business achieve its online goals.

Experience

Gyani Master
Founder
January 2021 - Present (3 years 5 months)
Nashik, Maharashtra, India

Vertex Furniture LLC Estimator and Digital Marketer February 2023 - Present (1 year 4 months)

Education

Savitribai Phule Pune University

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Civil Engineering · (2019 - 2022)